I did three sessions with Ricky around two months back and during the speed of
counselling in therapy he was extremely accommodating on my schedule he ensured that
I was present for the session emotionally and mentally and he had gained that trust
from me that I knew that he's committed to my growth and yeah and as a result of
these three sessions what changed in me was before the sessions I had become somewhat
reclusive I was restless I was smoking every alternate weeks and just after the sessions
I had dealt with a lot of trauma as a result of which I was more courageous than I
was before I was making decisions more easily I was able to draw boundaries learned to say
no one started saying no for certain things as a part of drawing boundaries I started to
become regular with my practices and you know exercise yoga meditation and with my schedule
I was overeating before the sessions and after the sessions that shifted for me now I'm
not eating anymore and all that happened just in three weeks so yep it was amazing thanks Ricky